Finding Aid for the William Campbell Binkley Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- 1 roll of microfilm, unidentified (Box 40 (7))
HAMER, P. M. (University of Tennessee, Works Progress Administration, National Archives, Southern Historical Association) - 20 (1931, 1933, 1935-38, 1940)
HAMILTON, Holrnan - 1 (May 6, 1946)
HAMILTON, J. G. de Roulhace (University of North Carolina Library) - 4 (1946, 1951)
HAMILTON, William B. (Duke University) - 12 (l^-W, 1950)
HAMLETT, Earl G. (Polk Street Methodist Church) - 1 (June 19, 1942)
HAMMOND, George P. (University of Southern California, University of New Mexico, University of California) - 16 (1932, 1933, 1940, 1943, 1951)
HAMMOND, H. W. - 1 (Aug. 25, 1933)
HAMMOND, Thomas T. (University of Virginia) - 1 (Apr. 3, 1962)
HAMNER, Laura V. (U.S. Post Office, Claude, Texas) - 1 (Jan. 27, 1921)
HANKE, Lewis (Library of Congress, Columhia University) - 6 (1941, 1963)
HANNA, A. J. (Rollins College, Southern Historical Association) - 18 (1942-48, n.d.)
HANNA, Kathryn Abbey (Florida State College for Women, Rollins College, Southern Historical Association) - 10 (1935, 1942-44, 1947, 1948, 1952)
HANNA, Paul L. (Journal of Politics) - 1 (Jan. 14, 1946)
HANSEN, Marcus L. (University of Illinois) - 2 (1935)
HARDACRE, Gracia - 3 (1951, 1961, n.d.)
HARDAGRE, Paul H. (Vanderbilt University) - 25 (1948-51, 1956, 1959, 1960, 1963, 1964, 1967-69, n.d.)
HARDY, Eric W. (Junior College of Augusta) - 2 (1941)
HARLAN, Louis R. (East Texas State College) - 3 (1958, 1959)
HARLOW, Ralph V. (Syracuse University) - 1 (May 29, 1943)
HARPER, Henry Winston (University of Texas) - 1 (Sept. 10, 1926)
HARRINGTON, Charles (Tulane University) - 1 (n.d.)
HARRINGTON, Fred Harvey (University of Arkansas) - 4 (1944, 1946, 1948, 1957)
HARRISON, H. V. - 1 (Feb. 15, 1940)
HART, Laura Louise (Vanderbilt University ) - 2 (1945, 1949)
HARTJE, Robert G. (University of Georgia, Wittenberg University) - 8 (1951-54, 1960, 1964)
HARWELL, Richard B. (Emory University) - 2 (1944, 1948)
HASKINS, Charles H. (Harvard University) - 1 (Mar. 12, 1926)
HASSETT, William D. (The White House) - 1 (June 8, 1950)
HAUN, Mildred (Nashville Tenriessean) - 1 (July 11, 1942)
HAY, Thomas Robson - 7 (l942-45)
HAYDEN, Carl (United States Senate) - 2 (1937, 1945)
HAYNIE, William B. - 2 (1937)
HAYS, Samuel P. (University of Pittsburgh) - 1 (June 13, 1962)
HAZARD, Lucy Lockwood (Mills College) - 2 (1936)
HEAD, Holman (University of Alabama) - 2 (Sept. 29, 1953)
HECK, Frank H. (Centre College of Kentucky) - 2 (1958)
HEGENER, Joseph - 1 (Aug. 27, 1921)
HEISEY, Ernest E. (Southern Methodist University) - 1 (Apr. 7, 1936)
HELDERMAN, L. C. (Washington and Lee University) - 1 (June 3, 1935)
HEMPHILL, W. Edwin (Virginia World War II Commission, Albemarle County Historical Society) - 4 (1945, 1946)
HENDERSON, Archibald (University of North Carolina) - 2 (1945)
HENDERSON, Gerald D. (Vanderbilt University) - 6 (1930, 1933, 1939)
HENDERSON, S. E. - 1 (Jan. 2, 1938)
HENDERSON, L. C. (Harlan High School) - 1 (Feb. 21, 1931)
HENDERSON, Zach S. (Georgia Teachers College) - 2 (1949)
HENDRICKSON, Walter B. (MacMurray College) - 1 (July 3, 1948)
HENRY, H. M. (Emory and Henry College) - 4 (1937, 1942, 1950) (including 1 from John Pomfret)
HENRY, Robert S. (Association of American Railroads) - 8 (1946, 1948, 1949) (including 1 from Monroe F. Cockrell)
HEPBURN, A. H. (Bobbs-Merrill Company) - 2 (1942)
HERSHEY, C. B. (Colorado College) - 12 (1925, 1927, 1934, 1935, 1944, 1953)
HERSTEIN, W. R. - 1 (Mar. 7, 1939)
HERTEL, K. L. (University of Tennessee) - 1 (Aug. 25, 1947)
HESLER, I. R. (University of Tennessee) - 1 (Apr. 5, 1935)
HESSELTINE, William B. (University of Wisconsin, Southern Historical Association) - 6 (1937, 1939, 1951, 1960) (including 1 from Ray A. Billington)
HEYMAN, Max L., Jr. - 1 (Jan. 21, 1948)
HEWLETT, James 11. (Centre College of Kentucky) - 1 (Oct 2, 1947)
HEXTER, J. H. (Washington University) - 1 (Dec. 3, 1957)
HIBBS, Max L. - 1 (Aug. 7, 1940)
HICKS, John D. (University of Wisconsin, Wisconsin State Historical Society, University of California) - 7 (1938, 1941, 1944, 1945)
HIDY, Ralph W. (Harbard University, Business History Review) - 5 (1958-60, 1962)
HIGGINBOTHAM, S. W. (Rice University, Journal of Southern History) - 7 (1945, 1963, 1966)
1IIGHSAW, J. L. (Memphis Technical High School) - 7 (1938, 1939)
HIGHSMITH, William E. (Louisiana State University) - 3 (l946, 1947)
HILDRICH, Joseph N. - 2 (1931)
HILL, Lawrence F. (Ohio State University) - 5 (1930, 1935, 1949, 1951, 1959)
HILL, Lister (U.S. Senate) - 1 (Apr. 28, 1951)
HILL, Louise B. (Bennett School of Liberal and Applied Arts) - 13 (1931-38)
HILLDRUP, R. L. - 1 (Feb. 2, 1945)
HITT, Homer L. (Louisiana State University in New Orleans) - 1 (Apr. 8, 1958)
HINTON, Kate - 1 (Apr. 22, 1965)
HOAGLAND, D. R. (University of California) - 1 (Oct. 23, 1958)
HODDEN, F. H. (University of Kansas) - 3 (1926, 1928)
HODGES, Arthur W. (Department of the Army) - 1 (July 6, 1950)
HOFFMAN, Donald B. (Phi Alpha Theta) - 1 (Apr. 5, 1951)
HOFFMAN, J. Wesley (University of Tennessee) - 2 (1945, 1950)
HOGAN, W. E. (Methodist Episcopal General Board of Christian Education) - 1 (May 19, 1937)
HOGAN, W. Murray (Nashville Chamber of Commerce) - 2 (1936, 1938)
HOGAN, William R. (Louisiana State University, University of Oklahoma, Tulane University) - 14 (1939, 1940, 194-46)
HOGGAN, David L. (American Institute, Munich) - 1 (Aug. 25, 1950)
HOLLANDER, Lee M. - 1 (June 5, 1933)
HOLMAN, Maude (Tennessee Department of Education) - 1 (Mar. 17, 1938)
HOLT, W. Stull (University of Washington) - 4 (1951, 1963)
HOOD, Cornelia - 1 (Jan. 23, 1938)
HOOKER, Richard J. (Central Y.M.C.A. College) - 2 (l943) (including 1 from W. H. Stephenson)
HOOLE, W. Stanley (University of Alabama) - 1 (Apr. 21, 1947)
HORN, Stanley F. (Southern Lumberman, Tennessee Historical Society) - 6 (1937, 1941, 1942, 1951) (including 1 each from Emma Farrell and S. C. Williams)
HORTON, Lucile Dee (County of El Paso) - 1 (May 29, 1930)
HOSKINS, James D. (University of Tennessee) - 1 (Oct. 25, 1934)
HOUSE, R. B. (University of North Carolina) - 1 (Apr. 12, 1949)
HOWE, Edmund G. (University of Alabama) - 1 (n.d.)
HOWE, George F. (University of Cincinnati) - 20 (1936-38) (including 1 each from Alston G. Field, M. M. Quaife, Louis B. Schmidt, Thomas P. Martin, 2 from Nelson Vance Russell)
HOWELL, Isabel (Vanderbilt University Library, Tennessee State Library and Archives) - 7 (1932, 1933, 1955, n.d.)
HOWELL, Morton B. (Insurance) - 1 (Oct. 22, 1956)
HOWELL, R. B. C. (State of Tennessee) - 2 (1937)
HOWARD, Mrs. T. L. - 1 (Mar. 26, 1936)
HOWER, Ralph M. (Harvard University) - 1 (Sept. 17, 1965)
HOYT, William D., Jr. (Loyola College) - 1 (Feb. 1, 1950)
HUBBARD, Preston J. - 1 (Jan. l8, 1954)
HUBBART, H. C. (Ohio Wesleyan University) - 2 (1938, 1939)
HUDSON, A. P. (University of North Carolina) - 1 (Oct. 17, 1938)
HUGHES, R. M. (Miami University) - 1 (Nov. 12, 1924)
HULBERT, Archer Butler (University of Chicago, Colorado College) - 33 (1923-31, n.d.) (including 1 each from John W, Oliver, E. A. Christian, and George A. Womack)
HUMPHREY, G. D. (Mississippi State College) - 1 (May 3. 1935)
HUNT, Douglas L. (Birmingham-Southern College) - 4 (1934, 1935, 1938)
HURD, R. C. (Marshalltown, Iowa, High School) - 1 (Aug. 29, 1925)
HURT, John Jeter (Union University) - 2 (1935)
HUSSEY, Roland D. (University of California) - 2 (1950)
HUTCHINSON, William T. (James Madison Papers) - 2 (1962)
IBBOTSON, J. S. (Rosenburg Library) - 2 (Oct. 26, 1936)
INAUGURAL Committee (Vanderbilt University) - 1 (Jan. 11, 1938)
INGRAM, Irvine S. (West Georgia College) - 3 (1952)
IRELAND, Gordon - 2 (1941)
IRONS, George V. (Howard College) - 1 (Apr. 23, 1946)
IVEY, John E., Jr. (Board of Control for Southern Regional Education) -1 (Nov. 14, 1949)
JACKSON, Dorothy V. (Mississippi Valley Historical Association) - 1 (Jan. 13, 1964)
JACKSON, George Pullen (Vanderbilt University) - 2 (1934, 1936)
JACKSON, Kenneth M. (Mount Saint Mary's College) - 7 (1937, 1939, 1940, 1946, 1951)
JACOBS, Wilbur R. (University of California) - 1 (Dec. 12, 1958)
JAMES, Herman (University of Texas) - 2 (1921, 1922)
JAMES, Joseph B. (William Woods College) - 2 (1943)
JAMES, Thelma - 1 (Sept. 17, 1942)
JAQUA, E. J. (Pomona College) - 1 (July 23, 1926)
JARMAN, Beryl B. (House of Representatives) - 1 (Aug. 21, 1945)
JARMAN, T. Wilson (Mary Baldwin College) - 1 (Apr. 28, 1943)
JEFFERSON, B. L. (University of Illinois) - 1 (May 7, 1929)
JEFFRIES, Charlie - 1 (Apr. 23, 19W
JEFFRIES, William W. (University of Mississippi, U.S. Naval Academy) -22 (1937, 1939, 1941-46, 1948, 1954-56) (including 1 from Felix Johnson)
JEMISON, Margaret (Emory University) - 1 (June 18, 1943)
JENKINS, William T. (Snead Junior College) - 1 (Feb. 12, 1957)
JEWETT, F. L. (Texas Bible Chair) - 1 (n.d.)
JOAN OF ARC, Sister (Our Lady of the Lake College) - 1 (July 12, 1945)
JOHANNSEN, Robert W. (University of Washington) - 2 (1950, 1951)
JOHNSON, Amanda (Georgia State College) - 1 (Nov. 18, 1948)
JOHNSON, Arthur M. (Cambridge School, Harvard University) - 19 (1947, 1949-54, 1957-59)
JOHNSON, Eldon L. (University of Oregon) - 2 (1951)
JOHNSON, J. G. (University of Colorado) - 1 (Nov. 26, 1928)
JOHNSON, Lewis K. (Washington and Lee University) - 1 (Sept. 24, 1947)
JOHNSON, Samuel A. (Kansas State Teachers College) - 1 (Apr. 1, 1936)
JOHNSTON, Frontis W. (Davidson College) - 1 (Feb. 2, 1950)
JONES, Allen F. (National Archives) - 2 (1937)
JONES, David Howell (Vanderbilt University Press) - 2 (1968)
JONES, R. F. - 1 (Sept. 19, 1922)
JONES, T. Marshall (Works Progress Administration) - 8 (1936-38, 1940, n.d.)
JONES, Virgil L. (University of Arkansas) - 2 (1954)
JONES, Warren F. (Winchester High School) - 1 (Feb. 14, 1931)
JORDAN, Lenore - 2 (1936, 1937)
JORDAN, Weymouth Tyree (Transylvania College, Cherokee Indian Normal School, Blue Mountain College, Judson College, Alabama Polytechnic Institute, Florida State University) - 157 (including 1 each from Lorena C. Goodrich and Dan M. Robison, and 3 from W. H. Stephenson)
JOSEPHSON, Bertha E. (Mississippi Valley Historical Review) - 12 (1934-36, 1939, n.d.)
KALMON, Ed and Marion - 4 (n.d.)
KAMPF, Louise F. (Colorado College) - 1 (July 11, 1947)
KANE, Nancy Hall (American Historical Review) - 1 (Jan. 2, 1957)
KARNES, Thomas L. (Tulane University) - 4 (1958, n.d.)
KARSCH, Robert F. (Westminster College) - 5 (1935-38)
KAYS, V. C. (Arkansas State A & M College) - 1 (Mar. 24, 1926)
KEARNEY, Thomas - 2 (1938, n.d.)
KEGLEY, Isabelle Green - 8 (1932, 1933, n.d.)
KEITH, Warren G. (Winthrop College) - 1 (Aug. 30, 1938)
KEHL, James A. (University of Pittsburgh) - 2 (1958)
KELLAR, Herbert A. (McCormick Historical Association) - 24 (1938, 1939, 1943, 1944, 1946, 1947, 1949, 1952, n.d.)
KELLAR, Lucille - 2 (1955)
KELLER, J. A. (Florence State Teachers College) - 1 (Apr. 28, 1939)
KELLY, Alfred H. (Wayne State University) - 1 (Feb. 26, 1957)
KENDRICK, B. B. (Women's College, University of North Carolina) - 1 (Feb. 5, 1943)
KENNEDY, John F. (U.S. Senate) - 2 (1957)
KENNEDY, Margaret - 1 (Feb. 17, 1930)
KERN, Jean B. (Mississippi Valley Historical Review) - 3 (1946)
KERR, Robert Erskine - 3 (1947, 1949, 1950)
KETRING, Ruth A. (Duke University Library) - 1 (Feb. 15, 1932)
KEY, D. M. (Millsaps College) - 5 (1935)
KIBLER, Lillian - 1 (Jan. 31, 1950)
KIGER, Joseph C. (American Council on Education, University of Alabama) - 4 (1951, 1953, 1961)
KILMAN, Ed (The Houston Post) - 1 (Feb. 2, 1940)
KIMBROUGH- Phillips Company (Doris Payne) - 1 (Sept. 2, 1953)
KIMMEL, Roy (Cherry Lawn School) - 4 (1927, 1929)
KINARD, F. M. (Clemson Agricultural College) - 2 (1946)
KINARD (Latimer), Margaret (William and Mary College, Clemson Agricultural College, University of Illinois) - 5 (1948, 1951-53, 1956)
KINCAID, Robert L. (Lincoln Memorial University) - 1 (Oct. 20, 1942)
KING, John O. (Ludlow Typograph Company) - 1 (Oct. 9, 1944)
KING, W. T. (Western Union Telegraph Company) - 1 (Nov. 5, 1936)
KIRKLAND, J. H. (Vanderbilt University) - 15 (1930, 1931, 1934, 1937) (including 2 from George B. Winton)
KIRKPATRICK, Olive - 2 (1951, 1953)
KIRWAN, A. D. (University of Kentucky) - 1 (Jan. 27, 1950)
KNIGHT, Edgar W. (University of North Carolina) - 3 (1947, 1948)
KNIGHT, Homer L. - 2 (1938, 1941)
KNAPP, Charles M. (University of Kentucky) - 1 (Sept. 25, 1935)
KNOWLES, George H. (Stanford University) - 2 (1943, 1951)
KOHLMEIER, A. L. (Indiana University) - 4 (1944-46)
KOM0DORE, Marianne - 3 (1956, 1957, 1958)
KOOKER, Arthur R. (Army Air Forces Training Command) - 1 (Sept. 22, 1943)
KOONTZ, Louis Knott (Pacific Historical Review, University of California) - 6 (1933, 1942, 1947, 1948, 1950)
KOWITZ, Gerald T. (University of Houston) - 2 (1965)
KOY, R. A. (U.S. Gypsum Company) - 1 (June 18, 1962)
KRAMER, Howard D. (Mississippi Valley Historical Review) - 1 (1942)
KREY, A. G. (University of Minnesota) - 1 (Feb. 10, 1949)
KRUEGER, E. T. (Vanderbilt University) - 1 (Mar. 15, 1937)
KUYKENDALL, Ralph S. (University of California, Hawaii Historical Commission, University of Hawaii) - 10 (1921-23, 1925, 1933)
KYTE, George C. (Phi Delta Kappa Fraternity) - 1 (Dec. 12, 1932)
LAKE, Devereaux - 1 (May 4, 1948)
LAMBETH, Walter (U.S. House of Representatives) - 1 (Apr. 29, 1937)
LAMKIN, R. L. (Farm Credit Administration) - 1 (July 30, 1934)
LANCASTER Press, Inc. (C.W. Wilson) - 13 (1932-33)
LAND, Aubrey C. (Princeton University, Vanderbilt University, University of Nebraska, London School of Economics and Political Science, University of Maryland) - 11 (1950, 1951, 1955-58, 1962, 1964)
LANG, Elfrieda (Indiana Magazine of History) - 1 (Apr. 28, 1949)
LANGDON, Robert M. (U.S. Naval Academy) - 1 (Oct. 7, 1947)
LANNING, John Tate (The Hispanic American Historical Review) - 2 (1942)
LAPHAM, M. E. (Tulane University) - 1 (July 23, 1963)
LAPRADE, W. T. (Duke University Press) - 1 (Feb. 10, 1945)
LARKIN, Thomas III (Larkin, Roosevelt & Larkin) - 1 (Aug. 17, 1946)
LARSON, Laurence (University of Illinois) - 2 (1925, 1928)
LARSON, T. A. (University of Wyoming) - 2 (1956)
LASSOV5ZKY, Ch. (Peter Pazmany University) - 1 (Sept. 5, 1947)
LAW, Robert A. (University of Texas) - 1 (Oct. 9, 1944)
LAWRENCE, Alexander A. (Georgia Historical Society) - 5 (1947)
LEACH, Henry Goddard (Committee on Cultural Relations with Latin America) 1 - (Feb. 2, 1930)
LEAVITT, Sturgis E. (Southern Humanities Commission) - 15 (1948-50) (including 2 from Philip Davidson)
LEE, Ronald F. (Department of the Interior) - 1 (Dec. 20, 1933)
LEE, Umphrey (Southern University Conference) - 2 (1947, 1948)
LeDUC, Thomas (University of Nebraska) - 1 (Nov. 22, 1951)
LEEBRICK, K. C. (University of Hawaii) - 10 (1920, 1922, 1925, 1927)
LEFLER, Hugh T. (University of North Carolina) - 1 (Jan. 7, 1950)
LEHMANN, Joseph H. (University of Alabama, U.S. Air Force University) -9 (1949, 1953, 1955, n.d.)
LELAND, W. C. (American Historical Association) - 1 (Sept. 9, 1919)
LEOPOLD, Richard W. (Northwestern University) - 1 (May 20, 1963)
LEVERET^ William E., Jr. (Indian Springs School) - 6 (1953, 1955, 1956, 1960)
LEVY, Lawrence H. (Hotel Claridge) - 2 (1939)
LEWIS, Anna (Oklahoma College for Women) - 1 (Apr. 1946)
LEWIS, L. L. (Oklahoma Agricultural and Mechanical College) - 3 (1920)
LINDGREN, Raymond E. (Occidental College, Vanderbilt University, University of Minnesota, City College, Princeton University, University of Wisconsin) - 48 (l945, 1947, 1949-57)
LINDLEY, Harlow (Ohio State Archeological and Historical Society) - 1 (May 25, 1944)
LINDSEY, David (Baldwin-Wallace College) - 2 (1947)
LINTON, Samuel E. (Tennessee Sons of the American Revolution) - 1 (Feb. 15, 1935)
LISTON, R. T. L. (Davis and Elkins College) - 2 (1942)
LITTLE, Helen - 1 (July 22, 1937)
LIVELY, Robert A. (Princeton University) - 9 (1950-52)
LLOYD, A. Y. (Morehead State Teachers College, Kentucky Department of Welfare) - 7 (1931, 1933, 1939)
LLOYD, E. Russell (Rhodes Scholarships) - 1 (Oct. 22, 1924)
LLOYD, Evelyn (State Historical... Society of Colorado) - 1 (Feb. 2, 1927)
LOCKWOOD, Frank C. (University of Arizona) - 2 (1932)
LOGSDON, R. E. (Memphis Chamber of Commerce) - 5 (1939)
LOLMAUGH, Nellie H. - 20 (1945, 1950-53, 1955, 1960, 1964, n.d.)
LONG, Linda - 1 (Mar. 2, 1964)
LONGENECKER, Herbert E. (Tulane University) - 3 (1962-64)
LONN, Ella (Goucher College, Southern Historical Association) - 13 (1935, 1943-46, 1948)
LORANT, Stefan - 1 (Nov. 24, 1947)
LORCH, Fred W. (Iowa State College) - 1 (Apr. 7, 1938)
LORD, Clifford L. (Wisconsin State Historical Society, American Association for State and Local History, Columbia University) - 23 (1951-56, 1958-60, 1964)
LORD, Robert H. (Harvard College) - 2 (1921, 1922)
LOUISIANA State University Press (Bruce F. Denbo) - 1 (Aug. 6, 1947)
LOVELL, Lois Campbell - 1 (Dec. 3, 1934)
LOVENTHAL, Lee J. (Loventhal Brothers) - 1 (Sept. 13, 1930)
LOVETT, Robert W. (Harvard University) - 1 (Oct. 31, 1962)
LOWE, Caroline - 1 (June 27, 1952)
LOWREY, Lawrence T. (Blue Mountain College) - 1 (Jan. 20, 1931)
LOWRIE, George W. (University of Minnesota) - 1 (May 15, 1922)
LOWRY, C. S. (Murray State Teachers College) - 1 (Nov. 16, 1942)
LUCHETTI, Dennis - l(Apr. 10, 1968)
LUCKETT, Wallace W. (National Park Service) - 7 (1930, 1931, 1933-35)
LUDLUM, Robert P. (A. & M. College of Texas) - 1 (Nov. 30, 1938)
LUMIANSKY, R. M. (Tulane University) - 5 (1959-63)
LUND, F. E. (State Teachers College, Florence) - 2 (1947)
LUNDE, Robert G. (University of Kentucky) - 2 (1938, 1939)
LUTZ, Ralph H. (Stanford University) - 1 (Aug. 8, 1952)
LYBYER, Albert H. (University of Illinois) - 1 (Sept. 17, 1935)
LYON, E. Wilson (Colgate University) - 1 (Oct. 16, 1938)
LYNCH, William O. (Indiana Historical Society) - 42 (1938, 1939, 1944-47, 1949, n.d.)
MacDONALD, H. D. (Kiwanie Club of Colorado Springs) - 2 (1926, 1928)
MacLEISH, Archibald (Librarian of Congress, Department of State) - 3 (1944, 1945)
MAGEE, Robert M. (Wayne University) - 1 (Apr. 9, 1945)
MAHORNER, Sue (Works Progress Administration) - 1 (nov. 9, 1938)
MADRON, Beverly B. - 2 (1961)
MADRON, Thomas William (Lambuth College) - 4 (1964, 1966)
MALONE, Carroll B. (Stanford University) - 2 (1930, 1931)
MALONE, Dumas (Dictionary of American Biography) - 11 (1930-33)
MAMATEY, Victor S. (Florida State University) - 1 (Apr. 8, 1965)
MANN, Albert H. (General Education Hoard) - 1 (Aug. 4, 1944)
MANNING, Thomas G. (Yale University) - 2 (1947, 1948)
MARKS, Alan J. (Plenum Publishing Company) - 1 (^ept. 3, 1969)
MARCHANT, Alexander (University of Texas, Vunderbilt University) - 17 (1949, 1950, 1952-54, 1956, 1958, n.d.)
MAtfLEY, Aime Bonner - 1 (Sept. 26, 1946)
MARQUIS, A. N. Co. - 2 (1925, n.d.)
MARSH, Philip (Miami University) - 1 (may 10, 1948)
MARSHALL, Thomas M. (Washington University) - 3 (1921, 1925, 1930)
MARTIN, Chester (American Historical Association) - 3 (1932)
MARTIN, Thomas E. (U.S. Congress) - 1 (July 27, 1945)
MARTIN, Thomas P. (Library of Congress) - 29 (1935, 1944, 1945, 1948, 1950, 1953, n.d.)
MARTIN, W. E. (Sullins College) - 1 (July 12, 1943)
MASON, K. H. - 1 (Apr. 30, 1946)
MASSEY, Mary Elizabeth (Washington College) - 1 (July 19, 1948)
MASTERSON, W. H. (Rice Institute) - 3 (1957, 1958)
MATEYKA, Melvin J. - 1 (Nov. 10, 1945)
MATHEWS, Joseph J. (Emory University) - 10 (1948-51)
MATHIAS, James F. (Guggenheim Foundation) - 3 (1949, 1953, n.d.)
MATTHEWS, Charles D. (Birmingham-Southern College) - 1 (May 7, 1942)
MAUELSHAGEN, Carl (University System of Georgia) - 2 (1946)
MAXEY & Donnelly Motor Co. (J. Ries Trathan) - 1 (July 17, 1953)
MAXWELL, George W. - 1 (June 12, 1930)
MAYER, Joseph (Joint Committee on Materials for Research) - 3 (1934)
MAYFIELD, G. R. (Vanderbilt University) - 1 (Jan. 15, 1938)
MAYO, Bernard (University of Virginia) - 4 (l943-45, 1949)
McABEE, Forrest L. (University of California Faculty Club) - 1 (Apr. 27, 1931)
McALISTER, Hill (Tennessee Executive Chamber) - 1 (Oct. 15, 1936)
McBRIDE, Robert M. (Tennessee Historical Quarterly) - 2 (1966)
McCAIN, J. R. (Agnes Scott College) - 1 (Nov. 30, 1950)
McCAIN, William D. (Mississippi Department of Archives and History) - 3 (1946, 1948)
McCALL, Abner V. (Baylor University) - 1 (May 20, 1965)
McCAMPBELL, Betsy - 6 (1955, 1956, 1958)
McCANN, Bess (Peabody College) - 1 (Mar. 28, 1932)
McCLOY, Shelby T. (University of Kentucky) - 1 (Jan. 20, 1950)
McCLURE, Stanley W. - 1 (Jan. 26, 1938)
McCONNELL, Roland C. - 1 (Dec. 16, 1946)
McCONNELL, W. J. - 1 (.Aug. 28, 1950)
McCRADY, Edward (University of the South) - 7 (1946-48)
McCULLOCH, Margaret C. - 1 (Oct. 12, 1946)
McCUTCHEON, Roger P. (Tulane University) - 1 (June 16, 1954)
McDANIEL, William R. (Works Progress Administration) - 1 (Dec. 30, 1938)
McDONALD, Forrest (State Historical Society of Wisconsin) - 8 (1956-59)
McDONALD, Kenneth M. - 9 (1937-39)
McDONALD, IL D. (Strang Garage Company) - 1 (Nov. 10, 1930)
McDONALD, Thomas N. - 1 (May 7, 1957)
McDONaLD, William E. (Herbert Hoover High School) - 2 (1935, 1936)
McFADDEN, Ed. T. (Commercial National Bank) - 7 (1931, 1940, 1950, n.d.) (including 1 each from Charles T. Fitts and W. M. Proctor)
McFADDEN, George W., Jr. - 8 (1925, 1927-29)
McGRANE, Reginald C. (University of Cincinnati) - 3 (1950, 1951, 1953)
McILWAINE, Robert S. - 1 (Oct. 8, 1926)
McKAY, S. S. - 2 (1921)
McKEITHAN, D. M. (University of Texas) - 8 (1944, 1945)
McKELLAR, Kenneth (U.S. Senate) - 1 (Apr. 28, 1937)
McKINLEY, Lela Ethel - 2 (1935)
McLAIN, Raymond F. (Eureka College) - 1 (May 20, 1939)
McLEAN, Ross H. (Emory University) - 7 (1935)
McLEAN, Winifred H. - 1 (Oct. 3, 1936)
McLEMORE, R. A. (Jones County Agricultural High School and Junior College, Judson College, Mississippi Southern College) - 55 (1933-39, 1941, 1943, 1944, 1946-51, 1953, 1956) (including 1 from Savoie Lottinville)
McLENDAN, J. H. - 1 (July 26, 1937)
McMILLAN, M. C. - 1 (Dec. 9, 1947)
McMURTRIE, Douglas C. (Committee on Historical Source Materials) - 1 (June 7, 1944)
McNEILL, W. H. - l (sept. 5, 1924)
McREYNOLDS, Sam D. (U.S. House of Representatives) - 1 (Apr. lb, 1938)
MEAD, Telfer L. (Saunders System) - 3 (1927, 1936)
MEADE, ROBERT D. (Randolph Macon women's College) - 2 (1944, 1947)
MEANEY, John W. (University of Texas) - 6 (1965) (including 1 from Dorrnan H. Winfrey)
MECHAM, J. Lloyd (Southwestern Social Science Association) - 1 (Oct. 13, 1933)
MENDELSON, Wallace (University of Tennessee) - 1 (May 7, 1947)
MENK, Patricia Holbert (University of Virginia) - 1 (July 11, 1945)
MERK, Frederick (Harvard University) - 2 (1964)
MERIWETHER, R. L. (University of South Carolina) - 1 (Apr. 6, 1928)
MERONEY, Geraldine - 5 (1947, 1949, 1953)
MERRIAM, John F. (Northern Natural Gas Company) - 2 (1963)
MERRILL, Horace S. (University of Maryland) - 3 (1965)
METZENTHIN, W. E. (University of Texas) - 1 (Sept. 4, 1936)
MEYER, Erwin Ferdinand (Chief) (Colorado College, University of Colorado) 51 (1922, 1924-30, 1932)
METCALF, K. D. (New York Public Library) - 1 (Jan. 19, 1935)
MIEROW, C. C. (Colorado College, Carleton College) - 21 (1924, 1925, 1929, 1930, 1937, 1943) (including 1 each from George G. Wilson, A. Lawrence Lowell, and Clarence Crane Brinton)
MILES, Edwin A. (University of Houston) - 3 (1959, 1960)
MILES, Guy - 1 (Feb. 17, 1972)
MILLEH, August C., Jr. - 1 (Jan. 25, 1948)
MILNAR, Anthony L. - 1 (Feb. 5, 1945)
MILTON, Abby Crawford (Current Historical Society of Tennessee) - 2 (1935)
MILTON, George Fort (The Chattanooga News) - 3 U938) (including 1 from Cordell Hull)
MIMS, Edwin (Vanderbilt University) - 2 (1955) (including 1 from Goodrich C. White)
MINTON, John D. (University of Miami) - 5 (1947, 1951)
MISCH, Fannie B. - 1 (Jan. 26, 1947)
MITCHELL, F. K. (Rhodes Scholarships) - 1 (Nov. 20, 1934)
MITCHELL, H. C. (West Virginia University, University of Maine) - 7 (1924-27, n.d.)
MITCHELL, Martha C. (Mississippi College) - 1 (Apr. 1, 1948)
MOE, Henry Allen (Guggenheim Foundation) - 3 (1955, 1958, 1959)
MOFFATT, Charles H. (Anderson City Schools, Marshall College) - 20 (l943-48, 1950-52)